export let answerBymentees = [
  {
    queAns: [
      {
        question: {
          question: "Which Phone You Likes !...",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "iPhone",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Nothing",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Samsung",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-07T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 7,
        },
        answer: ["iPhone", "Nothing"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          question: "Are you Intersted To Buy A Our Course?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 6,
        },
        answer: ["No"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532f93f45a0e09056dafa",
          },
          question: "Are you educated?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 5,
        },
        answer: ["No way"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532823f45a0e09056daf1",
          },
          question: "What are examples of transferable skills?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Communication",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Leadership",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Problem-solving",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 4,
        },
        answer: ["Communication", "Leadership"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a5324e3f45a0e09056daef",
          },
          question: "What are some common interview formats?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Panel interview",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Phone screening",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Group interview",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 3,
        },
        answer: ["Panel interview", "Phone screening"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a530dc3f45a0e09056daeb",
          },
          question: "What are some common examples of hobbies and interests that people pursue?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Sports and Physical Activities",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Creative Arts",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Travel and Exploration",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 4,
              option: "Gaming and Technology",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 1,
        },
        answer: ["Sports and Physical Activities", "Creative Arts"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a531ac3f45a0e09056daed",
          },
          question: "What is the concept of introversion and extraversion, and how do they differ?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option:
                "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Long Answer",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 2,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 2,
        },
        answer: [
          "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
        ],
      },
    ],
    user: "darshan",
    score: "",
  },
  {
    queAns: [
      {
        question: {
          question: "Which Phone You Likes !...",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "iPhone",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Nothing",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Samsung",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-07T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 7,
        },
        answer: ["iPhone", "Nothing"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          question: "Are you Intersted To Buy A Our Course?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 6,
        },
        answer: ["No"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532f93f45a0e09056dafa",
          },
          question: "Are you educated?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 5,
        },
        answer: ["No way"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532823f45a0e09056daf1",
          },
          question: "What are examples of transferable skills?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Communication",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Leadership",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Problem-solving",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 4,
        },
        answer: ["Communication", "Problem-solving"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a5324e3f45a0e09056daef",
          },
          question: "What are some common interview formats?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Panel interview",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Phone screening",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Group interview",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 3,
        },
        answer: ["Panel interview", "Group interview"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a530dc3f45a0e09056daeb",
          },
          question: "What are some common examples of hobbies and interests that people pursue?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Sports and Physical Activities",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Creative Arts",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Travel and Exploration",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 4,
              option: "Gaming and Technology",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 1,
        },
        answer: ["Sports and Physical Activities", "Travel and Exploration", "Gaming and Technology"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a531ac3f45a0e09056daed",
          },
          question: "What is the concept of introversion and extraversion, and how do they differ?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option:
                "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Long Answer",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 2,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 2,
        },
        answer: [
          "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
        ],
      },
    ],
    user: "tulsi",
    score: "",
  },
];

export let answerByMantors = [
  {
    queAns: [
      {
        question: {
          question: "Which Phone You Likes !...",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "iPhone",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Nothing",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Samsung",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-07T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:57:01.382Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 7,
        },
        answer: ["iPhone", "Nothing"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          question: "Are you Intersted To Buy A Our Course?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:09:14.881Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 6,
        },
        answer: ["No"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532f93f45a0e09056dafa",
          },
          question: "Are you educated?.",
          category: "Edcutions Informations",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "No",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "No way",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Single Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:08:09.279Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 5,
        },
        answer: ["No way"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a532823f45a0e09056daf1",
          },
          question: "What are examples of transferable skills?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Communication",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Leadership",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Problem-solving",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:06:10.247Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 4,
        },
        answer: ["Communication", "Problem-solving"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a5324e3f45a0e09056daef",
          },
          question: "What are some common interview formats?",
          category: "Career & Experience",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Panel interview",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Phone screening",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Group interview",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 3,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:05:18.344Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 3,
        },
        answer: ["Panel interview", "Group interview"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a530dc3f45a0e09056daeb",
          },
          question: "What are some common examples of hobbies and interests that people pursue?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option: "Sports and Physical Activities",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 2,
              option: "Creative Arts",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 3,
              option: "Travel and Exploration",
            },
            {
              optionNum: 4,
              option: "Gaming and Technology",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Multi Choice",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 4,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T08:59:08.649Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 1,
        },
        answer: ["Sports and Physical Activities", "Travel and Exploration", "Gaming and Technology"],
      },
      {
        question: {
          _id: {
            $oid: "64a531ac3f45a0e09056daed",
          },
          question: "What is the concept of introversion and extraversion, and how do they differ?",
          category: "Personality & Interests",
          option: [
            {
              optionNum: 1,
              option:
                "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
            },
          ],
          queType: "Long Answer",
          required: true,
          status: "Active",
          weight: 2,
          isDraft: false,
          createdAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          updatedAt: {
            $date: "2023-07-05T09:02:36.312Z",
          },
          __v: 0,
          isDel: false,
          orderNum: 2,
        },
        answer: [
          "Introverts tend to be more reserved, introspective, and prefer solitary activities. They gain energy from spending time alone and may feel drained in social situations",
        ],
      },
    ],
    user: "Gautam",
  },
];
